She was in a relationship before she left Manila?
그녀는 연애 중이었습니다 그녀가 마닐라를 떠나기 전에?
Peter Montevilla.
피터 몬테빌라.
Hey! Who are you?!
이봐! 당신은 누구입니까?!
Tell me why you're here,
여기 왜 왔는지 말해 보세요.
or I'll have you arrested for trespassing!
그렇지 않으면 당신을 체포하겠습니다 무단 침입을 위해!
Your brother!
네 형제야!
I think he has something to do why my father is missing!
내 생각엔 그 사람이 할 일이 있는 것 같아 왜 아버지가 실종됐나요!
His name is Sandro Soliman!
그의 이름은 산드로 솔리만입니다!
- When did he disappear? - It's been five months.
- 언제 사라졌나요? - 5개월이 지났습니다.
Who is Sandro Soliman?
산드로 솔리만(Sandro Soliman)은 누구입니까?
Don't you ever mention that name in this house.
당신은 언급하지 마세요 이 집에 그 이름이 있어요.
This conversation is over.
이 대화는 끝났습니다.
Get out!
나가세요!
Go away!
저리 가세요!
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[새소리]
[WATER SPLASHING]
[물이 튀는 소리]
[SARI SQUEALING] Ah!
[사리 비명소리] 아!
Congratulations! The curse is gone!
축하해요! 저주가 사라졌습니다!
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[밝은 음악 재생]
[SARI GIGGLING]
[사리 낄낄거림]
- Did your grandpa tell you? - No, I just know it.
- 할아버지가 말씀하셨나요? - 아뇨, ​​그냥 알고 있어요.
I believe the ritual my grandpa talked about is effective.
난 할아버지의 의식을 믿어요 얘기하면 효과적이다.
The ritual you performed?
당신이 행한 의식은요?
My neighbors did the same thing before.
내 이웃들이 그랬어 이전에도 마찬가지다.
Were they two friends who also tried to lift a curse?
그 둘은 친구였나요? 누가 저주를 풀려고 했나요?
Yes.
예.
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
Well, they became a couple, and eventually tied the knot.
자, 그들은 커플이 되었습니다. 그리고 결국 매듭을 묶었습니다.
And now, they have five children!
그리고 지금, 그들은 다섯 명의 자녀를 두고 있어요!
- Huh?! - What?!
- 뭐?! - 무엇?!
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[밝은 음악이 계속됩니다]
[SARI CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[사리가 부드럽게 웃는다]
Yes!
예!
Not only did they cast out bad luck,
뿐만 아니라 그들은 불운을 쫓아내
but they also found each other.
하지만 그들은 또한 발견 서로.
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG" BY ANGELA KEN PLAYING]
["파노 쿵 타요 나 랑" 작성자: 안젤라 켄 재생]
Wait.
기다리다.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐.
Wait, what if?
잠깐, 만약에?
[SARI SQUEALS]
[사리의 비명]
What if you two end up together, just like them?
둘이 결국엔 어떡하지? 같이, 그들처럼?
Why? It's possible, right?
왜? 가능하지 않나요?
You're friends. Plus, you're both single.
당신은 친구입니다. 게다가 둘 다 싱글이에요.
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG" CONTINUES]
["파노 쿵 타요 나 랑" 계속]
Universe!
우주!
Did the ritual bring together another pair?
의식이 하나로 모였나요? 또 한 쌍?
[SARI GIGGLES]
[사리 낄낄거림]
[JADE CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
[제이드가 어색하게 웃는다]
Come on, Sari.
어서, 사리.
It's probably a... case-by-case basis.
아마... 사례별로.
I don't think Kiko and I will share the same fate.
내 생각엔 Kiko와 나는 그렇지 않을 것 같아 같은 운명을 공유하게 됩니다.
That's so silly, Sari.
정말 바보같아, 사리.
Y-Yeah.
응-그래.
Not to mention, removing the bad luck
말할 것도 없이, 불운을 없애는 중
is what really matters.
정말 중요한 것입니다.
Shh!
쉿!
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG" CONTINUES]
["파노 쿵 타요 나 랑" 계속]
Sir Kiko!
키코 씨!
Sir Martin might be around and hear you!
마틴 경이 근처에 있을 수도 있어요 그리고 당신의 말을 들어보세요!
Okay, listen.
알았어, 들어봐.
Promise me, this conversation never happened.
약속해 이 대화 결코 일어나지 않았습니다.
Okay, bye-bye!
알았어, 안녕!
- Ouch. - Oh, sorry.
- 아야. - 아, 미안해요.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY] Be careful.
[부드럽게 웃는다] 조심하세요.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[테마 음악 재생]
[MONETTE] Hi, Gio.
[모네뜨] 안녕, 지오.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[새소리]
[MONETTE] Now, let me see.
[MONETTE] 자, 어디 보자.
[KIKO] Let's eat?
[키코] 먹자?
- Are you hungry? - [JADE] A little.
- 배고픈가요? - [제이드] 조금요.
- Where's the-- - Monette.
- 어디-- - 모네트.
About the guest who caused a ruckus...
손님에 대해서 소란을 일으킨 사람...
About Chase.
체이스에 대해서.
[GIO] His stuff is still with us.
[지오] 그의 물건은 아직도 우리와 함께 있습니다.
Shouldn't we turn it over to the local town hall?
뒤집어 볼까요? 동네 시청으로?
Not now.
지금은 아닙니다.
He's still our guest.
그 사람은 아직 우리 손님이에요.
Once he's sober, do you think you can talk to him?
일단 그가 술에 취하면 어떻게 생각하시나요? 그 사람이랑 얘기 좀 할 수 있어?
[MONETTE] Just use banana.
[MONETTE] 바나나만 사용하세요.
I don't think that's necessary.
나는 그것이 필요하다고 생각하지 않습니다.
We have a bigger problem.
더 큰 문제가 있습니다.
[JUSTIN CLEARS THROAT]
[저스틴이 목을 가다듬는다]
The bank has already sent a notice
은행은 이미 알림을 보냈어
about the hotel's debt.
호텔 빚에 대해서요.
Luna.
루나.
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[우울한 음악 재생]
[JUSTIN] Luna, we need to talk.
[저스틴] 루나, 우리 얘기 좀 해야 해.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[우울한 음악이 계속됩니다]
- Monette. - [MONETTE] Oh?
- 모네트. - [모네뜨] 아?
Are those two okay?
그 둘 괜찮나요?
Sounds like they were talking about the mess from last night.
그 사람들 얘기하는 것 같던데 어젯밤의 난장판에 대해.
They got into a fight?
그들이 싸웠나요?
No.
아니요.
It's about Luna's friend who's checking in with us right now.
루나의 친구에 관한 이야기입니다. 지금 바로 확인해보세요.
He got drunk and became rowdy.
그는 술에 취해 난폭해졌습니다.
Friend?
친구?
Hang on, I don't think she's mentioned a friend like that.
잠깐만요, 내 생각엔 그녀는 아닌 것 같아요 그런 친구를 언급했어요.
Well, I wouldn't be surprised if you didn't know him.
글쎄, 난 놀라지 않을 거야 당신이 그를 몰랐다면.
The things he was saying about Luna...
그 사람이 했던 말들 루나에 대해서...
Even Justin got caught up in the chaos.
저스틴도 따라잡았어 혼란 속에서.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[우울한 음악이 계속됩니다]
A lot of things have happened
많은 것 이런 일이 있었어
when we were away.
우리가 없을 때.
Needless to say, they've had a lot on their plate.
말할 필요도 없이 그들은 접시에 많은 것이있었습니다.
[JUSTIN] Luna, we need to talk.
[저스틴] 루나, 우리 얘기 좀 해야 해.
What for?
무엇 때문에?
So you can remind me just how messy my life is?
그러면 나에게 상기시켜 줄 수 있어요 내 인생이 얼마나 지저분한가?
No, Luna.
아니, 루나.
- I've learned about-- - No thanks, Justin.
- 내가 배운 것은-- - 괜찮아요, 저스틴.
I'm fine with what I've heard.
내가 들은 내용은 괜찮습니다.
Noted.
유명한.
By the way, aren't you suspended?
그건 그렇고, 정지된 거 아냐?
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[침울한 음악 재생]
Tsk.
쯧쯧.
We have a big problem.
큰 문제가 생겼습니다.
We're behind on the payment.
우리는 뒤쳐져 있어요 지불에.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[침울한 음악 재생]
Two months late.
두 달 늦었어요.
Is it possible to appeal for an extension?
이의신청이 가능한가요? 연장을 위해?
That's just an extension, Martin.
그건 그냥 확장 프로그램이야, 마틴.
We still need to find a way to be able to pay them.
우린 아직 방법을 찾아야 해 그들에게 돈을 지불할 수 있도록.
[LEON] At the moment,
[LEON] 지금은
money is only coming in from hotel operations.
돈만 들어오고 호텔 운영부터.
But the music festival brought in a nice profit, right?
하지만 뮤직페스티벌은 좋은 이익을 얻죠, 그렇죠?
Yes, but we had to give discounts
응, 하지만 우리는 그랬어 할인을 하려고
to everyone inconvenienced by that dead rat.
불편하신 모든 분들께 그 죽은 쥐 때문에.
And after the fiasco involving Chase and Justin.
그리고 실패 이후 체이스와 저스틴이 포함됩니다.
We've already spoken to Justin.
우리는 이미 얘기했어요 저스틴에게.
He's temporarily suspended from hotel duties.
그는 일시적으로 정지되었습니다 호텔 업무부터.
But that alone won't solve our problem.
하지만 그것만으로는 해결되지 않아 우리의 문제.
[LEON] So we need activities
[LEON] 그럼 활동이 필요해요
- that are low-cost, - [PHONE CHIMES]
- 비용이 저렴하고, - [전화 차임]
but have a high return.
하지만 수익률이 높다.
Promos that will lead to bookings.
이끌어줄 프로모션 예약에.
Anyone got ideas to help the hotel generate money?
누구에게나 도움이 될만한 아이디어가 있습니다 호텔이 돈을 벌어?
All suggestions are welcome.
모든 제안을 환영합니다.
[MARTIN] Uncle, have you read the proposal?
[MARTIN] 삼촌, 그랬나요? 제안서를 읽으셨나요?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[침울한 음악이 계속됨]
Do we have a deal?
우리 거래가 있나요?
[LEON] However, we need to talk before we pursue it.
[LEON] 하지만 얘기는 좀 해야겠어 우리가 그것을 추구하기 전에.
Yes. We'll decide together as a team.
예. 우리가 결정할게요 팀으로 함께.
Martin?
남자 이름?
Huh? Yeah.
뭐? 응.
Alright, I'll come up with something.
알았어, 내가 올라갈게 뭔가로.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[침울한 음악이 계속됨]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[전화 차임]
[RONALD] Let's meet again. Bring Sari.
[RONALD] 또 만나요. 사리를 가져오세요.
Sir, I'm really interested in your bar.
선생님, 정말 관심이 있어요 당신의 바에서.
And from the moment I saw it,
그리고 그것을 본 순간부터
wow, I immediately saw its potential.
와, 바로 봤어 그 잠재력.
[SCOFFS] It's true.
[비웃음] 사실이에요.
I just feel bad letting it go.
그냥 놔둬서 기분이 안 좋네요.
But family comes first.
하지만 가족이 먼저입니다.
I also need to move to America.
나도 움직여야 해 미국으로.
That's understandable.
그것은 이해할 수 있습니다.
So maybe we can talk about the contract...
그럼 우리 얘기 좀 할 수 있을 것 같아 계약에 대해...
[JUSTIN] Do they think I'd be sad
[저스틴] 내가 슬퍼할 거라고 생각할까
about being suspended?
정지당한 것에 대해?
I didn't even want to be there anyway.
난 원하지도 않았어 어쨌든 거기 있기 위해.
Oh, wait a second, bro. Yeah, yeah.
아, 잠깐만요, 형. 응, 응.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[전화 신호음]
- Bro, how are you? - Bro.
- 형, 잘 지내요? - 형.
- Where did you come from? - From the hotel.
- 어디서 오셨나요? - 호텔에서.
- Anyway, this is Trixie. - I know her.
- 아무튼 트릭시입니다. - 난 그 사람을 알아요.
Oh?
오?
Ah, she's the one you were talking about...
아, 그 사람이 바로 그 사람이야 당신이 말한 것은...
Mhm, that's her.
음, 그 사람이에요.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[소프트 음악 재생]
What did he say? What--
그가 뭐라고 말했습니까? 뭐--
I'll go ahead, bro.
내가 먼저 갈게, 형.
- Let's grab a drink later. - Alright.
- 나중에 한잔 하자. - 괜찮은.
Justin.
저스틴.
Justin, wait--
저스틴, 잠깐만--
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[소프트 음악 재생]
What did he say about me?
그 사람이 나에 대해 뭐라고 말했어요?
[GASPS] Sir!
[GASPS] 선생님!
This is more than my daily wage!
이건 내 일당보다 많은 액수야!
You don't want it?
당신은 그것을 원하지 않습니까?
Thank you, sir.
감사합니다.
Thank you so much.
매우 감사합니다.
Sir, do you want anything?
선생님, 원하는 것이 있나요?
I can get you coffee.
커피 사드릴 수 있어요.
Or lunch? My treat.
아니면 점심? 내 대접.
My boss gave me an incentive.
상사가 나에게 인센티브를 주었다.
You know what, just keep that.
그거 알아요. 그냥 보관하세요.
Prepare for our next meeting with Uncle Ronald.
다음 회의를 준비하세요 로널드 삼촌과 함께.
We have another meeting?
우리 또 회의 있어요?
Shh! Oh--
쉿! 아--
Sari, what did I tell you?
사리야, 내가 뭐라고 말했지?
[WHISPERS] We have another meeting?
[속삭임] 우리 또 회의 있어요?
Yes.
예.
And you're coming.
그리고 당신은오고있다.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[기발한 음악 재생]
What do you mean you changed your mind?
무슨 뜻이야? 마음이 바뀌었나요?
We were this close to a sale.
우리는 판매에 이만큼 가까웠습니다.
- Sir? - Sorry.
- 선생님? - 죄송합니다.
I think I'll just give it to someone else.
그냥 줄 것 같아요 다른 사람에게.
What exactly did Justin tell you?
저스틴은 정확히 무엇을 했나요? 말해봐?
Is that why you changed your mind?
그래서 당신이 변한 건가요? 당신의 마음?
Actually, Justin is kind.
사실 저스틴은 친절해요.
He's helped me a lot.
그는 나에게 많은 도움을 주었습니다.
That guy? Really?
그 사람? 정말?
It's not obvious, but yes.
분명하지는 않지만 그렇습니다.
It's actually the first time he's asked me for a favor.
사실 처음이에요 그는 나에게 부탁을 했어요.
A favor against me. Am I right?
나에 대한 호의입니다. 내가 맞나요?
[SIGHS] Not really.
[한숨] 그렇지 않아요.
I just trust Justin's judgment.
저는 저스틴의 판단을 믿을 뿐입니다.
If he says it's okay to sell it to you,
그 사람이 괜찮다고 하면 당신에게 팔려고요
then I'll give it to you.
그럼 내가 너에게 줄게.
So you mean I have to convince him?
그럼 내가 가지고 있다는 뜻이군요 그를 설득하려고?
Yes.
예.
Justin is kind.
저스틴은 친절해요.
You won't have a hard time.
당신은 어려움을 겪지 않을 것입니다.
Alright, kids, just keep eating, okay?
알았어, 얘들아, 그냥 계속 먹어, 알았지?
- [GIGGLES] - Okay.
- [낄낄거림] - 알았어.
Thank you, Miss Jade.
고마워요, 제이드 씨.
Oh no, don't thank me.
아뇨, 감사하지 마세요.
Thank Sir Edward. He's the one who gave that.
에드워드 선생님께 감사드립니다. 그 사람이 그걸 준 사람이에요.
- Thank you, Sir Edward.
- 고마워요, 에드워드 경.
- Just eat, okay? - Just keep eating.
- 그냥 먹어, 알았지? - 계속 먹어요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Edward, pork buns?
에드워드, 돼지고기 빵?
Thanks for the lunch date.
점심 데이트에 감사드립니다.
Wow.
우와.
That's the first time you thanked me.
그건 처음이야 당신은 나에게 감사했습니다.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[소프트 음악 재생]
You know, out of all our lunch dates,
아시다시피, 무엇보다도 우리 점심 데이트,
this one is my favorite.
이것은 내가 가장 좋아하는 것입니다.
I'm just not the one you want to date.
난 그냥 그런 사람이 아니야 당신은 데이트하고 싶어.
What's that?
그게 뭐야?
Nothing. I said let's just finish our lunch.
아무것도 아님. 난 그냥 하자고 했어 점심을 마무리해요.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
Edward, are you okay?
에드워드, 괜찮아?
Is there... something wrong?
혹시... 뭔가 잘못된 걸까요?
I get it.
알겠습니다.
So you're really not going to share, huh?
그럼 너 진짜 안 갈 거야 공유하려고, 응?
Didn't you say...
말하지 않았나요...
...we only share what we want to share?
...우리는 공유만 합니다 우리가 공유하고 싶은 것은 무엇입니까?
There's no forcing, right?
강요는 없지 않나요?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
How are things at the hotel?
호텔 상황은 어때요?
Well...
음...
...a lot of things didn't go well.
...많은 것 잘 안 됐어요.
Like?
좋다?
Well...
음...
...a guest caused a scene.
...손님이 소동을 일으켰습니다.
But the bigger problem is the bank notice.
하지만 더 큰 문제는 은행 통지서입니다.
But don't worry about that.
그러나 그것에 대해 걱정하지 마십시오.
We'll handle it. It's okay.
우리가 처리하겠습니다. 괜찮아요.
How's your leave?
휴가는 잘 지내시나요?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[침울한 음악 재생]
It's okay.
괜찮아요.
I was able to do what I needed to do.
나는 할 수 있었다 내가해야 할 일.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[침울한 음악이 계속됨]
Alright.
괜찮은.
Let's finish this lunch date.
오늘 점심 데이트를 마치겠습니다.
Someone might get upset.
누군가는 화를 낼 수도 있습니다.
Huh?
뭐?
[SCOFFS] Who?
[비웃음] 누구요?
How would I know?
내가 어떻게 알 수 있나요?
Who would get upset? My siblings?
누가 화를 내겠는가? 내 형제 자매?
Why would they get mad?
왜 그들은 화를 낼까요?
- You're funny. - Not them.
- 당신은 재밌어요. - 그 사람들은 아니야.
I'm talking about someone else.
나는 다른 사람에 대해 이야기하고 있습니다.
Like a boyfriend?
남자 친구처럼?
Is that what you mean?
그게 무슨 뜻인가요?
[BOY] Oh, look, a balloon!
[소년] 아, 보세요, 풍선이요!
Come on!
어서 해봐요!
Run!
달리다!
Let's go!
갑시다!
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG?" BY ANGELA KEN PLAYING]
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG?" 작성자: 안젤라 켄 재생]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[목이 맑아진다]
Hello, friends. My name is Kiko.
안녕, 친구들. 내 이름은 키코입니다.
Kiko, is this for us?
키코, 이거 우리꺼야?
It's no one's birthday.
누구의 생일도 아닙니다.
[KIKO] Are balloons only for birthdays?
[키코] 풍선인가 생일에만?
Yes.
예.
Alright, then let's just pretend it's your birthday.
알았어, 그럼 그냥 척하자 그것은 당신의 생일입니다.
Happy birthday!
생일 축하해요!
- Thank you!
- 감사합니다!
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Let's play!
놀자!
Give me the blue one!
파란색을 주세요!
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG?" CONTINUES PLAYING]
["PAANO KUNG TAYO NA LANG?" 계속 재생]
That's why you're so interested in this.
그렇기 때문에 당신은 이것에 너무 관심이 있어요.
The kids are so fun to be around with.
아이들이 너무 재미있어해요 함께 있기 위해.
But, why are you here?
그런데 왜 여기에 있는 걸까요?
I don't like ghosts.
나는 유령을 좋아하지 않는다.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[소프트 음악 재생]
Ghost? Where? Is there a ghost? What ghost?
귀신? 어디? 유령이 있나요? 무슨 유령?
No, Jade...
아니, 제이드...
I have something to tell you.
당신에게 할 말이 있습니다.
What's that?
그게 뭐야?
Because, Jade...
왜냐하면, 제이드...
[CHILD] Aunty Jade!
[어린이] 제이드 아줌마!
Oh. [CHUCKLES]
오. [웃음]
Wow!
우와!
Wow, did you do this?
와, 이거 했어?
What is this?
이게 뭔가요?
[CHILD] That's you and Uncle Kiko!
[어린이] 그게 바로 너야 그리고 키코 삼촌!
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
Ah.
아.
- That's us? - [CHILD] Yes!
- 그게 우리야? - [어린이] 네!
You and your boyfriend are adorable.
당신과 당신의 남자친구는 사랑스럽다.
Boyfriend? Oh gosh. [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
남자 친구? 아 이런. [긴장해서 낄낄거림]
You know, your drawing is beautiful, but...
알다시피, 당신의 그림은 아름답지만...
we're not dating!
우리는 데이트 안 해요!
He's not my... boyfriend! [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
그 사람은 내... 남자친구가 아니야! [긴장해서 낄낄거림]
[CHILD] He isn't your boyfriend? Then what is he to you?
[어린이] 그 사람이 네 남자친구 아니야? 그렇다면 그 사람은 당신에게 어떤 존재인가요?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
Um... well...
음... 음...
best friend!
가장 친한 친구!
Kiko and I are best friends!
키코와 나는 가장 친한 친구예요!
[CHILD] Really, Uncle Kiko?
[어린이] 정말요, 키코 삼촌?
Huh? [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
뭐? [긴장해서 낄낄거림]
Yeah..
응..
Mhm-hmm. Jade and I are best friends.
음-흠. 제이드와 나는 가장 친한 친구입니다.
Mhm-hmm. [CHUCKLES]
음-흠. [웃음]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
Hey, Cheska. Come on, please. You have to talk to Justin.
안녕, 체스카. 어서, 제발. 저스틴과 얘기해 보세요.
Why do I have to talk to him?
내가 왜 그 사람이랑 얘기해야 하는데?
Ah, please, please, please, please, please, please.
아, 제발, 제발, 제발, 제발, 제발, 제발.
Pretty, please...
예쁘네요...
You did something, didn't you?
당신은 뭔가를 했죠, 그렇죠?
Nothing.
아무것도 아님.
You did something. What did you do?
당신은 뭔가를 했어요. 당신은 무엇을 했나요?
Nothing!
아무것도 아님!
You know what? I know you, you're lying.
그거 알아? 나는 당신을 알고 있습니다. 당신은 거짓말을하고 있습니다.
You are a strong independent woman.
당신은 독립심이 강한 사람입니다 여자.
You could talk to him before, but why can't you do it now?
그 사람이랑 전에 얘기 좀 해볼 수도 있었을 텐데, 그런데 왜 지금은 못 합니까?
What's wrong?
무슨 일이야?
Well, because...
글쎄요...
Because?
왜냐하면?
Because I said something to him.
내가 그에게 뭔가 말을 했기 때문이다.
Like what exactly?
정확히 어떤가요?
I said something mean to him.
나는 그에게 뭔가 나쁜 말을 했다.
Like what?
어떤가요?
Well...
음...
Whatever! I said something to him.
무엇이든! 나는 그에게 뭔가를 말했다.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
Bad things, Cheska!
나쁜 일이네, 체스카!
Harsh words.
가혹한 말.
I hurt his feelings.
나는 그의 감정을 상하게했습니다.
Ah!
아!
That is why you were both off when we were with Maria!
그래서 둘 다 꺼져 있었어 우리가 마리아와 함께 있었을 때!
I knew it! That's why he wasn't bothering you!
나는 그것을 알고 있었다! 그렇기 때문에 그 사람은 당신을 괴롭히지 않았어요!
Yes, yes. Don't rub it in.
예, 그렇습니다. 문지르지 마세요.
Why do I need to talk to him?
내가 왜 그 사람과 얘기해야 하죠?
Hey, hey, hey. Come on, come on!
안녕, 안녕, 안녕. 어서, 어서!
Talk to him, please?
그 사람한테 얘기 좀 해주세요.
It will be easier for both of you, if you apologize.
둘 다 더 쉬울 거예요 당신이 사과한다면.
[SIGHS] Sorry?
[한숨] 죄송해요?
Why do I have to apologize? If he didn't talk to the bar owner,
내가 왜 사과해야 합니까? 만약에 그는 술집 주인과 얘기하지 않았어
I wouldn't have had this problem in the first place.
이런 문제는 없었을 텐데 우선.
Huh?
뭐?
You're both confusing. You're both adults, fix it yourselves.
둘 다 혼란스러워요. 당신은 어른 둘 다 스스로 고치세요.
You'll just apologize.
그냥 사과하시면 됩니다.
Oh my gosh.
맙소사.
Fine, fine, okay, fine. I'll apologize.
알았어, 알았어, 알았어, 알았어. 사과하겠습니다.
Whatever.
무엇이든.
If there's a bar...
술집이 있다면...
if the bar is there...
바가 있다면...
you'll be the manager, okay?
네가 매니저가 될 거야, 알았지?
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[감미로운 음악 재생]
[SCOFFS] Manager.
[비웃음] 매니저.
It's true!
사실이에요!
You don't want to believe me? Give that to me.
내 말을 믿고 싶지 않아요? 그거 나한테 줘.
If the bar arrives and you'll be the manager,
바가 도착하면 그러면 당신이 관리자가 될 거예요,
you don't have to do jobs like this anymore.
넌 일을 할 필요가 없어 더 이상 이렇게.
Don't you like that?
당신은 그것을 좋아하지 않습니까?
I wouldn't be the manager, if you don't own the bar.
나는 매니저가 되지 않을 것이다. 바를 소유하지 않은 경우.
You need to buy it.
당신은 그것을 구입해야합니다.
That's the point.
그게 요점입니다.
You have to convince Justin.
저스틴을 설득해야 해요.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
- I'll think about it. - Don't think about it.
- 생각해 볼게요. - 생각하지 마세요.
- Come on. - I need to think about it.
- 어서 해봐요. - 생각해볼 필요가 있어요.
Tsk.
쯧쯧.
Okay, okay. I'll do it.
알았어, 알았어. 내가 할게요.
- That's great, isn't it? - Really?
- 정말 멋지지 않나요? - 정말?
Yes. Let me clean this. Give me a bit of peace, please.
예. 이것을 청소하겠습니다. 나에게 약간의 평화를 주세요.
[SPRAYING]
[살포 중]
- Thank you, Cheska. - Sure.
- 고마워요, 체스카. - 확신하는.
- Just Justin, right? - Yeah, just him. I promise.
- 그냥 저스틴이죠? - 응, 그 사람뿐이야. 약속해요.
- Oh, good game, Martin! - Good game, Uncle.
- 오, 잘했어, 마틴! - 잘했어요, 삼촌.
Gerard really got his competitiveness from you.
제라드가 정말 얻었어 그의 경쟁력은 당신에게서 나옵니다.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[소프트 음악 재생]
Well, I really wished he got...
글쎄, 난 정말 바랬어 그는...
my instincts in business.
나의 사업 본능.
[CHUCKLES]
[웃음]
Uh...
어...
and speaking of business,
사업 얘기가 나와서 말인데,
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[흥겨운 음악이 계속됩니다]
I'll go straight to the point.
바로 본론으로 들어가겠습니다.
I have my reservations on Hotel 88.
예약이 있어요 호텔 88에 있습니다.
We can discuss the terms, Uncle. If that's what you want.
용어에 대해 논의해보겠습니다, 삼촌. 그것이 당신이 원하는 것이라면.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[흥겨운 음악이 계속됩니다]
- [CHAIR SCRAPING] - Sit.
- [의자 긁기] - 앉으세요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Your proposal is great on paper.
당신의 제안은 훌륭해요 종이에.
But I also know what happened to your bookstore.
하지만 나도 알아요 네 서점에서 일어난 일이야.
I know the hotel is different from the business you handled...
호텔이 다르다는 걸 알아요 당신이 처리한 사업에서...
with your father, Carlos.
네 아버지 카를로스와 함께.
I talked to him.
나는 그와 이야기를 나눴다.
How can I be sure that this won't happen to my investment?
내가 이것을 어떻게 확신할 수 있는가? 내 투자는 안 될까?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[생각에 잠긴 음악 재생]
Well...
음...
Oh, I was just going to get the menu.
아, 방금 가려고 했는데 메뉴를 받으러
No. Sari, it's okay.
아뇨. 사리, 괜찮아요.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[소프트 음악 재생]
Ah, Uncle...
아, 삼촌...
- [TRIXIE] Okay. - [CHESKA] Hey, hey, hey!
- [트릭시] 알았어. - [체스카] 야야야야야!
Hey, I'm still working! My shift's not done yet!
아, 나 아직 일하는 중이야! 내 근무시간은 아직 끝나지 않았어!
There he is.
저기 있어요.
Go talk to Justin, hurry.
가서 저스틴에게 얘기해 보세요. 서둘러요.
Go on.
계속하세요.
[CHESKA] Friend!
[체스카] 친구!
Justin!
저스틴!
Hey, Justin, my friend!
안녕, 저스틴, 내 친구!
What are you up to? Want to hang out?
무슨 일을 하고 있나요? 어울리고 싶나요?
Are you busy with your business?
사업 때문에 바쁘신가요?
Maybe next time.
아마도 다음번에.
I just need to get some stuff here.
난 그냥 받아야 해 여기에 몇 가지 물건이 있습니다.
Are you going to Kaluguran?
칼루구란에 가시나요?
No.
아니요.
I just don't want to be here. My sister suspended me.
난 그냥 여기 있고 싶지 않아요. 내 여동생이 나를 정지시켰어요.
What?! Why are you suspended? What happened?
무엇?! 정지된 이유는 무엇인가요? 무슨 일이에요?
Oh, nothing.
아, 아무것도 아니야.
Just message me when you're in Kaluguran.
언제쯤 메시지를 보내주세요. 당신은 칼루구란에 있어요.
Let's hang out there.
거기서 놀자.
Take care, my friend.
조심해, 친구.
- [MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING] - Yes? Yes, yes, yes?
- [멜로우 음악 재생] - 응? 응, 응, 응?
Fail.
실패하다.
He's not in the mood.
그는 기분이 아니다.
Oh my God.
맙소사.
[TAKES A DEEP BREATH]
[심호흡을 한다]
What now?
지금은 무엇입니까?
[MARTIN] Uncle, you know the hotels are so much
[마틴] 삼촌, 아시죠? 호텔이 너무 많아
more lucrative than the bookstores right now?
것보다 더 수익성이 좋다 지금 서점?
Daily cashflows, higher margins duiring peak season,
일일 현금 흐름, 더 높은 마진 성수기를 앞두고
and the demand is steady for business travels, and tourism.
그리고 수요는 꾸준하다. 출장, 관광.
Especially with Hotel 88, since it's well-known in the area.
특히 호텔 88의 경우 그 지역에서는 잘 알려져 있어요.
What we're trying to do
우리가 하려는 일
is pushing for higher revenue potential for the hotel.
더 높은 수익을 추구하고 있습니다 호텔의 가능성.
Because it's not only the hotel rooms making money,
왜냐하면 그 뿐만이 아니기 때문입니다. 호텔 객실에서 돈을 벌고
there's also revenue from food, events,
수익도 나고 음식, 이벤트,
and the various vacation services we offer.
그리고 다양한 휴가 우리가 제공하는 서비스.
That's right, sir! Sir Ice is right!
그렇죠, 선생님! 아이스 선생님 말씀이 맞습니다!
I mean, uh...
내 말은, 어...
...Martin's right. He's absolutely right.
...마틴 말이 맞아요. 그는 절대적으로 옳습니다.
The hotel's music festival just ended,
호텔의 뮤직 페스티벌 방금 끝났어요
and it was a huge success.
그리고 그것은 큰 성공이었습니다.
Lots of people attended, and got rooms in the hotel.
많은 분들이 참석해주셨는데요, 그리고 호텔에 방을 얻었습니다.
"Your success?"
"당신의 성공은요?"
Of course, Uncle!
물론이죠, 삼촌!
His success is my success.
그의 성공은 나의 성공이다.
Well...
음...
I'm waiting for an answer.
답변을 기다리고 있습니다.
I'll think about what you told me.
생각해 볼게 당신이 나에게 말한 것.
We're definitely looking forward to working with you, Uncle.
우리는 확실히 기대하고 있습니다 당신과 함께 일하게 되어요, 삼촌.
Let's order some food.
음식을 주문해보자.
Uh, waiter?
어, 웨이터?
Sari, don't be shy.
사리, 부끄러워하지 마세요.
Order anything you want.
원하는 것을 주문하세요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[불안한 음악 재생]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[목이 맑아진다]
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
[휴대폰 벨소리]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[긴장된 음악 재생]
What did you find out?
무엇을 알아냈나요?
I found Sandro Soliman's previous home address.
산드로 솔리만(Sandro Soliman)을 찾았어요 이전 집 주소.
Okay. Send it to me.
좋아요. 나에게 보내주세요.
I'm checking out.
체크아웃 중이에요.
[RECEPTIONIST] Okay, sir.
[접수 담당자] 알겠습니다.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[음악이 계속됨]
Your brother is here?
당신의 동생이 여기 있나요?
Are you a lookout? You're working with him?
당신은 감시자입니까? 그 사람과 함께 일하시나요?
You want to know where your father is,
당신이 알고 싶은 것 네 아버지는 어디 계시니,
and what my sister knows? l'll help you.
그리고 내 여동생이 무엇을 알고 있나요? 내가 도와줄게.
Where were you and Martin?
당신과 마틴은 어디에 있었나요?
Your move to talk to Uncle Ronald,
대화하려는 당신의 움직임 로널드 삼촌,
that was a bit sneaky.
좀 은밀했어요.
This is what you do after our "team building activity?!"
다음에 할 일은 다음과 같습니다. 우리의 "팀 빌딩 활동?!"
- What are you talking about?! - They were here first.
- 무슨 소리를 하는 거야?! - 그 사람들이 먼저 여기에 있었어.
I'm just fighting back.
나는 단지 반격하고 있을 뿐입니다.
You've done nothing but get in our way!
당신은 아무것도 하지 않았습니다 하지만 우리를 방해해!
Why don't you try to understand what I'm trying to achieve?!
이해하려고 노력하지 그래? 내가 달성하려는 것이 무엇입니까?!
I'm only trying to protect my family!
나는 단지 노력하고 있을 뿐이다 내 가족을 지켜주세요!
And I'm trying to protect the hotel!
그리고 나는 노력하고 있어요 호텔을 보호하세요!